Let's talk about the dice that are used for craps.
Just to make sure that everybody is up to snuff on the situation.
You got two six sided dice.
Let's look at one of them.
There's a one.
Two dots so that's two.
There's three.
Four.
Five and then six.
And you've got two of these dice.
Two identical dice, right and the object is to roll them both at the same time.
That's the action that you do and you let rolling the dice or rolling the bones decide your fate if you will and that, there you have it.
There's six plus four equals ten so the whole deal is you're playing with two six sided dice and probability is at play and the thing, the combination, the sum that most often comes up will be seven because it's most likely with two six sided dice to get a seven than anything else.
Essentially, that's what's at play in craps.